词：2KM
//
曲：2KM
编曲：橘子海Orange Ocean
//
制作人：橘子海Orange Ocean
录音师：橘子海Orange Ocean
//
录音棚：陋室音乐L.O.W Studio
混音师：李天衣
//
吉他：2KM
贝斯：小路
//
鼓：卿溪
键盘：卿溪
//
母带后期：John Davis@Metropolis Studio
Upset
我心烦意乱
Cold wet
且寒冷潮湿
I just gonna feel alright
但这感觉刚好
This time
这一次
Love bites
锥心之爱
Wild roses in my hand
就如我所持玫瑰
Somehow
不知为何
Realize
幡然醒悟
Father's calling down
天父在召唤
This time
这一次
Love blinds
盲目之爱
Wild roses in my hand
就如我所持玫瑰
I travel all the town
我从远方而来
From afar
踏遍整座城市
Idol's falling down
看神明坠落凡间
Into the dust
化为渺渺尘埃
You lie you lie in
你身在谎言之中
Such a beautiful
美妙如斯
Don't cry don't cry
别哭 亲爱的
I put my summer in your hand
我的整个盛夏都在你掌心
I travel all the town
我从远方而来
From afar
踏遍整座城市
Idol's falling down
看神明坠落凡间
Into the dust
化为渺渺尘埃
I travel all the towns
我自远方星辰而来
From a star
游历所有的城市
Idol's falling down
看神明跌落凡间
Into the past
坠入无尽往昔